Guide to the Benedict Anderson papers, 1965, 1998
Anderson, Benedict Anderson papers,
- Series V. Miscellaneous documents and course material
  - Notices for Culture and Politics and Java in a Time of Revolution, 1971-1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Scanned newspaper articles and book reviews (1972 - 1975; 1984); typescript draft; Handwritten and typed correspondence (1971-2); journal publication (1973); reprint (1973)
  - Culture and Politics Financial Affairs, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Typed financial statement (1970); typescripts (1968; 1970)
  - Reviews of 'Imagined Communities', 1983-1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Scanned typescripts (1983-8); scanned newspaper articles (1983-4); newspaper (1983-4; 1988)
  - Personal Collection in Djakarta/USA (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Typed statement of puppets owned
  - Transfix Corrections Idea of Power (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Typescript draft with marginalia
  - Ruth-Ben Book Material (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Typescript draft with evident typed-in edits
  - Revenge (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Nationalism Notes, 1984-1989 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Scanned typescripts, one with handwritten notes on backside (1988-9); scanned newspaper article (1984)
  - Nationalism 2: 1 of 2, 1961-1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Thesis; typescripts, some with marginalia (1961; 1973; 1977; 1980-3); correspondence concerning "Imagined Communities" edits and correspondence (1982-3); partial draft of "Imagined Communities;" book contract memorandum
  - Nationalism 2: 2 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Train/Theatre, 1982-1992 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Scanned typescript w/ images
  - Military Bibliography, 1970-1989 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Military, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Student paper; notes about Turkey
  - USA, 1971-1983 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Notes (for course?); table graph (1979); scanned newspaper article (1975; 1981; 1983); newspaper (1971; 1976; 1980-3); correspondence (1980); journal publication (1979); scanned typescript (1980)
  - Warsaw Pact (1), 1982 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Warsaw Pact (2), 1982 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Handwritten Stuff on US Army Sales, 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Manuscript notes (1967 - 1971); scanned bulletin (1970); other scanned typescripts (1969 - 1971)
  - Nationalism, 1989-1992 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    Newspaper (1992); typescripts, some as drafts (1989)
  - US Military Stuff, 1953-1980 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Scanned typescripts (1953 - 1965); report (1986); table graph (1978 - 1980)
  - Military - Articles on (general non-Indonesian), 1965-1971 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    Notes; typescripts (1967; 1970); journal publication (1965); reprints (1965; 1968); bibliography (1967); promotional material (1971)
  - Indonesian National Army (Box 37, Folder 20)
    Copy of typescript "Presumably created by the Indonesian Delegation to U. N.’s..." (George Kahin files)
  - Asian Studies 602 Materials, 1978-1981 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    Reading list (1981); grey literature typescripts; scanned and unscanned (1978-9); notes; and
  - Biography/Autobiography, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    Notes; correspondence with students; scanned typescript (1986)
  - Government 300 Socialism, 1956-1973 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    Notes; reading list; typescript (1956); syllabi (1968-9; 1973)
  - Government 550 Spring 1974 A - Siegel, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Reading list (1971); scanned typescripts
  - Government 605 Spring 1981, 1977-1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Syllabi and course notes; article photocopies
  - Government 644 BRA - Spring 1973, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    Student papers with bibliographies
  - Govt. 647, Political Anthro. Fall '88, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    syllabus, class notes, photocopied review article ("Burma")
  - Indonesia Seminar (AS602) (I), 1964-1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Notes; scanned typescripts (1976)
  - Indonesia Seminar (AS602) (II), 1965-1986 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Typescript with comments; scanned typescripts (1965); reprints (1985; 1986)
  - Modern Indonesian Politics 1986, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Notes; syllabus; scanned typescript
  - Plural Socs Bahan, 1973-1983 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Scanned articles, chapter copies and typescripts (1973; 1981) [some marginalia]
  - 550 Spring 1984 Materials, 1980-1984 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Scanned newspapers (1983); notes; scanned news articles (1980)
  - 601 Reading Lists, 1975-1987 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Notes; readings lists (1975; 1978-81; 1984; 1987); correspondence (1987)
  - 601 1987, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    Reading lists; notes; correspondence with students; typescript (1987)
  - 602 Spring 1984 Bahan, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - 605 Spring 1982, 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Notes; syllabi; photocopied articles and book chapters [some marginalia]
  - Australia Lectures, Undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    Notes; some on note cards
  - Cambodia Lectures, 1980-1986 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    Typescripts, some as drafts (1986); journal publication (1980); news articles (1980-1); notes
  - Govt 344 Exams, 1967-1976 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Exam questions (1967 - 1976)
  - Great Britain Lectures, Undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - India Lectures, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Notes; typescript (1955)
  - Nigeria Lectures, Undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Pakistan Lectures, Undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
    Notes; written note cards; news article (1969)
  - SEA General Lectures, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    Notes, written and typed; newspapers (1974)
  - South Africa Lectures, Undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Thailand Lectures (1), 1969-1980 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Thailand Lectures (2), 1969-1981 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Vietnam Lectures (1), 1965-1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    News articles (1969; 1972; 1980); notes; typescript (1976); periodical (1975); newspapers (1965; 1969); reprint (1965)
  - Vietnam Lectures (2), 1965-1980 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 100.2 79 (1), 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Notes, written and typed; class syllabi (1977-80); scanned typescripts
  - 100.2 79 (2), 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Harian Rakjat newspapers, 1964-11-25-1965-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 1-10)
  - Berita Yudha newspapers, 1965-03-15-1965-05-17 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Duta Majarakat newspapers, 1965-03-08-1965-05-20 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Indonesian Herald, 1963-11-18-1963-12-30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Other Indonesian newspapers, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Berita Yudha
  - Malaysian Newspapers, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    The Straights Times, Malayan Times
  - Asian Newspapers, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - African Newspapers, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Egyptian, Nigerian
  - American Newspapers, 1965-06 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - English Newspapers, 1965-06 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Indian Newspapers, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - News Missives, 1964-12-1965-06 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Indonesia Today, 1964-09-1965-06 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Wartabhakti newspapers, 1963-11-23-1965-07-18 (Box 2, Folder 1-17)
  - Le Monde, 1964-05-08, 1965-06-21 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Le Monde Diplomatique, 1964-05 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - A Second Look at Southeast Asia speech, 1965-08-25 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Speech given by Arifin Bey, the Editor-in-Chief of the Indonesian Hearld, to the American Mens' Association.
  - Reflections upon the Indonesian Revolution article, 1964-03; Sukarno (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Research cards (Box 3)
    A1-B4
  - Research cards (Box 4)
    B5-C7
  - Research cards (Box 5)
    C9-D12
  - Research cards (Box 6)
    D13-E16
  - Research cards (Box 7)
    E17-F20
  - Research cards (Box 8)
    F21-G24
  - Research cards (Box 9)
    G25-H28
  - Research cards (Box 8)
  - Research cards (Box 9)
  - Research cards (Box 10)
    H29-I32
  - Research cards (Box 11)
    J33-K36
  - Research cards (Box 12)
    K37-L40
  - Research cards (Box 13)
    L41-L44
  - Research cards (Box 14)
    M45-M46
  - Research cards (Box 15)
    N49-N52
  - Research cards (Box 16)
    O53-O56
  - Research cards (Box 17)
    P57-P60
  - Research cards (Box 18)
    Q61-Q64
  - Research cards (Box 19)
    R65-R68
  - Research cards (Box 20)
    S69-S72, Removed S70 since it was empty except for one card which was moved to the end of S69 - Moved S72 into the same file as S71
  - Research cards (Box 23)
    T73
  - Research cards (Box 21)
    T74-T76
  - Research cards (Box 22)
    U77-U80
  - Research cards (Box 23)
    V82-V83